workthesystemacademy.com 2012-11-08

# Privacy Policy : Work The System Academy

## Work the System Academy

### Privacy Policy

BACKGROUND:

This Policy applies as between you, the User of this Web Site and Work the System Consultants Ltd (WTSC Ltd) the owner and provider of this Web Site. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of the Web Site and any Services or Systems therein.

Definitions and Interpretation

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:

“Account” means collectively the personal information, Payment Information and credentials used by Users to access Material and / or any communications System on the Web Site;  
“Content” means any text, graphics, images, audio, video, software, data compilations and any other form of information capable of being stored in a computer that appears on or forms part of this Web Site;  
“Cookie” means a small text file placed on your computer by Work the Ststem Consultants Ltd when you visit certain parts of this Web Site. This allows us to identify recurring visitors and to analyse their browsing habits within the Web Site. Further details are contained in Clause 10 ;  
“Data” means collectively all information that you submit to the Web Site. This includes, but is not limited to, Account details and information submitted using any of our Services or Systems;  
“Name” means Work the System Consultants Ltd trading as Work the System Academy  
“Service” means collectively any online facilities, tools, services or information that Work the System Consultants Ltd makes available through the Web Site either now or in the future;  
“System” means any online communications infrastructure that Work the System Consultants Ltd makes available through the Web Site either now or in the future. This includes, but is not limited to, web-based email, message boards, live chat facilities and email links;  
“User” / “Users” means any third party that accesses the Web Site and is not employed by Work the System Consultants Ltd and acting in the course of their employment; and  
“Visitors and Authorised visitors” Visitor is any person visiting the site but who does not transact any business; authorised visitor is any person who not only visits the site but also transacts business;  
.“Web Site” means the website that you are currently using www.workthesystemacademy.com and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.

General Statement We understand that privacy is important to users of our website. This statement governs our privacy policies regarding those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business, and also for Visitors who register to transact business on the Site (“Authorized Customers”) and who make use of the various services provided by Work the System Consultants Ltd  
What information is collected

Personally Identifiable Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, Social Security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information that is not connected to an identified individual.  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: bill to and ship to names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses and credit card information needed to authorize purchases and transact payments for products and services.

3.Third Party Web Sites and Services

3.1 WTSC Ltd may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment handling, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The providers of such services may have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Web Site. Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that WTSC Ltd requests. Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties must be processed within the terms of this Policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 .

3.2 We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

4.Changes of Business Ownership and Control

4.1 WTSC Ltd may, from time to time, expand or reduce its business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any division so transferred, be transferred along with that division and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.

4.2 In the event that any Data submitted by Users will be transferred in such a manner, you not be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.

5\. Access to your Data

You may at any time amend your Data either through the login area of the site (for Account holders) or by requesting amends directly via our support team. You may need to modify or update your Data if your circumstances change. Additional Data as to your marketing preferences may also be stored and you may change this at any time.

6\. Your Right to Withhold Information

6.1 You may access certain areas of the Web Site without providing any Data at all. However, to use all Services and Systems available on the Web Site you may be required to submit Account information or other Data.

6.2 You may restrict your internet browser’s use of Cookies. For more information see Clause 10 below.

7\. Accessing your own Data

7.1 You may access your Account at any time to view or amend the Data. You may need to modify or update your Data if your circumstances change. Additional Data as to your marketing preferences may also be stored and you may change this at any time.

7.2 You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal Data on payment of a small fee.

8\. Security Data security is of great importance to WTSC Ltd and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected online.

9\. Cookies

9.1 WTSC Ltd may set and access first-party Cookies on your computer. Cookies that may be placed on your computer are detailed in Schedule 1 to this Policy. These Cookies are integral to the services provided by the Web Site to you.

9.2 You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your web browser. By default, your browser will accept Cookies, however this can be altered. For further details please consult the help menu in your browser. Disabling Cookies may prevent you from using the full range of Services available on the Web Site.

9.3 You may delete Cookies, however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Web Site more quickly.

10\. Changes to this Policy

WTSC Ltd reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Web Site and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the Policy on your first use of the Web Site following the alterations.

11\. Links

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, or you ask us to forward information to a third party site on your behalf, you are moving to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
